irbureau.com 2015-06-26

# IRBureau Privacy Policy, Privacy Policy, Internet Research Bureau Pvt. Ltd. | IRBureau

IRB is firmly committed to protect your privacy and avoid the dissemination of your personal information. You can directly contact us via e-mail in case of any concerns related to our privacy practices at privacy@irbureau.com

IRB respects the privacy of people and persons associated with our campaign. We have a robust privacy policy in place to protect your personally identifiable information collected on IRB site(s). According to IRB policy we do not collect your personally identifiable information when you visit the website; however we may collect some non-personally identifiable information such as internet service provider, operating system, internet browser, IP address, your geo location and domain of your internet service provider for webpage optimization and monitor the visitors on our website. All these data help us determine the authenticity and credibility of the participant so that we receive only correct accurate and reliable data.

The personally identifiable information collected by IRB remains only with IRB and is not sold or transferred to anyone outside the company.   

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information**  
  
IRB uses the your personally identifiable information only to contact you for new business prospects, company updates via newsletters and answering to your queries & quotation.  

**Use of Cookies**  
  
IRB doesn’t capture or use your cookies to collect your personally identifiable information.  

**Agreement with Privacy Policy**  
  
By visiting this site, you agree to IRB’s privacy policy. If you do not agree to our privacy policy, we would suggest you not to use this website. We review our privacy policy time to time and reserve rights to change or update our Privacy Policy anytime. You should frequently visit this page so that you are updated about our latest Privacy Policy.
